[music]
>> Welcome. My name is Blazej Kotelko and
in this short session we'll talk about
user experience and changes that you see
on your screen when working with
Business Central.
First thing that you will notice is the
new icon Business Central icon updated
now in this year uh
that aligns with all the other changes
across Microsoft. You will see a lot of
different uh icon changes across uh
other Microsoft products and that also
applies to Business Central. You will
see this new icon when you're working
with Business Central through the
browser or when you are accessing
Business Central through a mobile app or
Teams app. Wherever you have Business
Central, this new icon uh is with you.
But of course the changes in the icon uh
is not the only thing that we have done.
And we mostly have uh focused on
uh working with agents on on experience
when you are working with agents in
Business Central.
So let's start with that.
You will see a new task pane for agents
and dedicated task pane that right now
is uh separated from the rest of the
experience
uh and allows you to work with agents
that are built in in the product sales
order and payables agents
but also those custom agents that can be
now built by you or or your partners.
There are other sessions in this event
that talk about specifically about
agents and also those custom agents
uh but I just wanted to highlight this
new experience where tasks related to
agents
uh are managed in this special uh
dedicated task pane.
Uh when we're looking at this task pane
we we have activities related to all of
those agents and sometimes agent needs
some
uh input from users uh and that's where
other experiences also um
are important.
So one of those changes you will see is
a new column on lists and especially uh
important when you are looking at
documents that were created by agents.
This new system columns give you a uh
information a short information about
who created a record and and who uh
modified the record.
And of course uh is available for you on
all lists not only
uh lists that uh talk about documents
created by agents. So it might be quite
useful uh for all the other use cases.
Uh another change that you will see is
the review bar that now shows up in
uh in the context of agents
specifically. So when the there is a
document or a page that that requires a
human intervention or a page that was
changed by the agent and now a human
operator would like to understand what
was changed and when uh that review bar
uh gives you additional um input into
what what has changed.
So let's see those little things in a
demo.
Here I am in my Business Central and I
can see that my agents already are
working for me.
As you can see right now I have this
dedicated task pane
and that task pane shows me all the
action activities from the agent.
If I click on a specific um
action and I have a purchase invoice
to review and I can see this
um review bar right now on screen.
So if I would
navigate to this
uh document uh from Business Central, I
would also get to to that review bar and
I will be able to review changes done by
the agent.
If I would go to my document list
let's go to sales quotes.
As you can see here I have this new
column created updated by.
You can turn this column on and off
using a new setting here in the list
settings.
And then here you can see which record
was created by a sales order agent or
another agent and which record was
modified maybe by uh a user.
This gives you a very quick access to
information about what was happening
with a specific document.
Uh very interesting changes related to
agents and uh and UI. Another thing that
you will see uh in the product is a new
action to cancel all agent tasks.
This is specifically very important if
you misconfigure your agent or uh for
some reason your agent is stuck and you
have plenty of tasks. Uh of course so
far you were also able to
uh navigate to each task and cancel uh
cancel it but right now you can cancel
everything
uh in one go and we have this stop all
tasks uh action available right now in
this dedicated task pane.
Uh we are actually also working on some
changes related to this task pane and
we'll be adding more actions like that
uh allowing you to control
um all the tasks coming from agents. So
uh please uh please be mindful about
about those uh those uh improvements
coming your way.
You will also see some changes in the
product that reflect our new feedback
experience. When we are asking for
feedback either uh randomly we actually
asking feed for feedback for customers
from time to time um and we are looking
forward to feedback coming from
customers
uh that uh that are running Business
Central in the cloud. But we also have
this on-demand feature where you can
provide feedback and then in some uh
areas of the product you will see this
new
uh feedback button where you can provide
a more detailed comments and even attach
a screenshot attach a document and that
way send us more information about your
experience with Business Central. That
helps uh tremendously uh improve
Business Central
over the long run.
That's it from my side. Thank you very
much. Have a look at all the resources
available for you uh
online
and
uh let's stay in touch.